Design is essential
in today's world.
设计在当今世界是至关重要的，
It defines your experiences
and your emotions.
它决定了你的体验和情感。
So we challenged ourselves to
create a design that was not
所以我们挑战自我，创建了一个
just for Android
phones and tablets.
不仅仅适用于Android手机和平板的设计理念。
We worked together-- Android,
Chrome, and across all
Android，Chrome 以及谷歌的其他产品部门一起合作
of Google-- to craft
one consistent  vision
构建了一个适配移动、桌面
for mobile, desktop, and beyond.
甚至更广泛设备的一致的设计。
We wanted a design that
was clear and simple,
我们希望有一种简明的、
and that people would
intuitively understand.
人们一目了然的设计。
So we imagined, what
if pixels didn't just
让我们想象，假如像素不仅仅有颜色
have color, but also depth?
而且有深度，这会怎样？
What if there was an
intelligent material that
假如有这么一种智能化的材料
was as simple as paper but
could transform and change
外观像纸片一样，却能够响应触摸
shape in response to touch?
来变化形状和内容，会怎么样？
And this led us to
a way of thinking
这就将我们引入了一种思维方式
that we call material design.
我们称之为“Material Design”
[APPLAUSE]
We drew inspiration
from paper and ink.
我们从纸墨汲取灵感
However, unlike real
paper, our digital material
却不同于真实的纸片，我们的数字材料
can expand, reform, and
reshape intelligently.
可以智能地伸展、重塑、变形。
The material has physical
surfaces and edges
这些材料具有物理的表面和边缘
because the human mind is wired
at its most primitive level
因为人的思维依赖用最原始的方式
to instinctively
understand objects
去本能得了解对象
and their relationships.
与他们之间的关系。
Those scenes and
shadows provide meaning
这些情景和阴影为人们提供了
about what you can touch
and how it will move.
操作的指引以及这些对象的运动方式。
In the real world, every small
change in position and depth
在现实世界中，位置和深度的每一次小调整
creates subtle but
important changes
都会对光影产生微妙但重要的改变。
in lighting and shadows.
So as part of the L preview,
we'll now allow app developers
作为L预览版的一部分，我们允许开发者
to specify an elevation
value for any UI surface,
指定任意UI表面的高度
and the framework will render
it in correct perspective
之后系统框架会应用虚拟光源和实时阴影
with virtual light sources
and real time shadows.
以正确的透视角度来呈现他们。
[APPLAUSE]
Material design is
beautiful and bold
Material design既华丽又大胆
because clean,
typographical layouts
因其简洁的、类似印刷品的布局
are simple and
easy to understand.
非常容易被用户理解。
Your content is the focus.
你的内容会很自然得成为焦点。
So the L preview will
allow app developers
L预览版让开发者
to easily colorize all
framework elements in your app
轻松地为所有框架元素上色
to match the theme
to your brand.
将应用程序的主题与你的品牌相匹配
And we're previewing
a new support library
我们正在测试一个新的、称之为“调色板”的支持库
that we call Palette to easily
extract colors from image
可以轻松的从图像中提取颜色
and really put those vivid
pictures front and center.
将生动详实的图片置于屏幕中最重要的地位。
We're giving designers familiar
tools like baseline grids
现在提供设计师们熟悉的基线与网格工具
that work across screens.
来划分和规划屏幕的内容。
Grids ensure apps have
a consistent rhythm
网格使应用具有一致的特征
and character, and
this will allow
这将允许
you to start with a
design on a phone,
设计师轻松地将手机上的设计
and logically and easily bring
that same design to tablets
带到平板和桌面上。
and laptops.
Now, one design doesn't
mean one size fits all.
不过，这并不意味着一个不变的设计将应用于所有场合，
Our guidelines allow you to
appropriately adapt the UI,
我们的设计指南将会允许你将UI调整到最恰当的形式
so your users will already
know their way around your app
这样你的用户很容易学会如何使用你的应用
no matter what
screen they use it on
不管他们用哪种屏幕
And we've also updated
our system font, Roboto,
我们也更新了系统字体Roboto
so that designers and developers
can use one type face designed
现在设计师和开发者可以在任何屏幕上
and optimized for every screen,
from your watch to your laptop
使用重新设计和优化的字体，从手表到桌面
to your television.
甚至电视机。
So now let's talk
about animation.
让我们来谈谈动画效果。
It's delightful when your
touch is rewarded with motion,
当用材料表面的移动来响应你的触摸，
and material
surfaces slide around
是多么令人愉悦啊。
with the physics of
card stock, but they
看起来像真实的一堆纸片，
respond to touch with
splashes of virtual ink
但它们却能通过虚拟墨水的扩散响应触摸，
that are like ripples in a pond.
就像池塘里泛起的涟漪。
As part of the L preview, all of
your application's UI building
作为L预览版的一部分，你的应用程序的UI模块
blocks have been updated to
include rich, animated touch
已经被丰富生动的动画触摸反馈代替。
feedback.
[APPLAUSE]
And no detail is too small to
bring a smile to your face,
越多的设计细节，越多的感动
like when the reload button
loops around or the playback
比如环绕的刷新按钮、
controls can change.
变化的返回键……
Finally, in the real world,
nothing teleports from one
最后，在现实世界中，没有什么可以远距离传送
place to another, and
that's why it's so important
这就是为什么屏幕上的每一个变化
to animate every
change on screen
都要靠动画来呈现
in a way that makes sense.
我们认为这很有意义。
In the L preview,
Android developers
在L预览版中，Android 开发者
will now be able to
create seamless animations
可以创建无缝的动画
from any screen to any other
between activities, and even
在不同的事件界面之间
between apps.
甚至在不同的应用之间。
[APPLAUSE]
So you're probably wondering
how this looks like in practice.
所以你一定想看一看这一设计理念具体是怎样实践的
We're going to give
you a sneak peak at one
接下来我们会给大家简单展示一下
of our familiar
Google applications
我们熟悉的谷歌应用程序
in the new material design.
是如何应用Material Design的。
Here you can see,
step by step, how
我们来看，如何一步一步
we update the design--
the typography,
更新设计——重新排版
the grid changes, and finally,
the surfaces and bold colors.
调整格局，最后，改变表面形态和大胆的用色。
And a few small changes make
a really big difference.
一些小小的改变，让应用焕然一新。
And you can also
see how easy it is
你也看到了
to take that same design
to different screens.
将相同的设计适配多种屏幕是多么简单。
Now, I've talked
about only a few
目前我只是介绍了一些
of the highlights of
material design and just some
Material Design 中的亮点
of the APIs that you can try
out in the Android L preview.
和一些你能在L预览版中使用的API
But as we all know, people
spend an enormous amount of time
但是我们都知道，人们花费大量时间
on the web, and
especially the mobile web.
在互联网上，尤其是移动互联网。
Last year at I/O, we
announced Polymer,
去年的开发者大会，我们发布了Polymer
which was a powerful new
UI library for the web.
一个全新的、功能强大的用于Web的UI素材库。
Today, we're bringing you
all of the material design
今天，我们带来了全新的Material Design
capabilities to the
web through Polymer.
通过Polymer，同样适用于Web上的设计
As a web developer, you'll
be able to build applications
作为一个Web开发者，你可以使用Material Design中的构件
out of material
design building blocks
设计你的应用
with all of the same
surfaces, bold graphics,
一样大胆的外观和图形
and smooth animations
at 60 frames per second.
以及高达60帧每秒的流畅动画。
So between the L
preview and Polymer,
有了L 预览版和Ploymer
you can bring the same
rich, fluid material design
你可以将同样丰富、流畅的Material Design
to every screen.
带到每一块屏幕。
And to help you take full
advantage of this framework,
为了让你们充分利用这个框架
we've also completely
redesigned and created
我们为每一种屏幕和设备
one unified set of style
guidelines for every screen
设计编写了全新的设计指南。
and for all devices.
These guidelines will help
designers and developers
这些指南将有助于设计师和开发者
alike understand best
practices and build
找到构建一致、美观的应用体验的
consistent, beautiful
experiences.
最佳的实践方式。
We're releasing the first draft
of these guidelines as part
我们今天发布了设计指南的第一个草稿
of our preview today
at google.com/design.
在google.com/design
[APPLAUSE]